<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WhaleTheDvaa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vulnerability_selection">Vulnerability Selection</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vuln_selection">Vulnability Selection</string>
    <string name="flag">Enter Flag</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tfa_killer">tfaKiller</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="viewSocial">Victim\'s Social account</string>
    <string name="AboutTheWhale">White Hat Application for Learning and Evaluation, or WHALE, is a tool to help you
        learn about how common Android app vulnerabilities can be exploited and mitigated. This app aims to help you
        understand how you can develop secure Android applications by avoiding common design flaws or protecting against
        common attacks, as well as improve your skills as a penetration tester conducting an evaluation of an app’s
        security.
    </string>
    <string name="flags">The progress page is where you can enter the flags you have found from the vulnerabilities. You
        can find this page through the main vulnerability selector, or the difficulty selector for each vulnerability.
        Press ‘Enter Flag’ to add the flag you have found. You can view your progress in the progress bars which display
        how many of the vulnerabilities you have completed overall, as well as broken down by difficulty level.
    </string>
    <string name="l33tSpeak">When you have successfully exploited a vulnerability, you will find a flag – a piece of
        text in leet speak, or “L33T SP34K”, such as 4PPL3S or B4N4N4S. Once you have this flag, enter it in the
        progress page to update your progress.
    </string>
    <string name="mitigation">On the difficulty selector page, you can view how your chosen vulnerability is caused and
        commonly mitigated. This explains which flaws allow an attacker to exploit the application, and how they can be
        fixed to prevent these kind of attacks.
    </string>
    <string name="vulnerabilties">When you select ‘Get Splashing’, you will be directed to the vulnerability selection
        page. Here you will see the range of common Android vulnerabilities WHALE offers for you to try and exploit,
        each with varying levels of difficulty – easy, medium, and ‘killer’.
    </string>
    <string name="hints">Each vulnerability comes with three hints that can be viewed by selecting the ‘Hints’ button in
        the top right. The three hints will progressively give away more clues as to how you can exploit the
        vulnerability and get the flag.
    </string>
    <string name="information">At the top right of each page is the information button whcih gives information about the
        vulnerability. This will give you your scenario as a hacker trying to exploit the app, including any of the
        details about your victim you may need, such as their email address. This will appear when you open the
        vulnerability, as well as any time you click this button.
    </string>
    <string name="progress">The progress page is where you can enter the flags you have found from the vulnerabilities.
        You can find this page through the main vulnerability selector, or the difficulty selector for each
        vulnerability. Press ‘Enter Flag’ to add the flag you have found. You can view your progress in the progress
        bars which display how many of the vulnerabilities you have completed overall, as well as broken down by
        difficulty level.
    </string>
    <string name="instructions">instructions
    </string>
    <string name="hint1EPA">People sometimes use a name of someone they know or a significant date as their as their pin.
    </string>
    <string name="hint2EPA">Dates can be formatted in several different ways eg.
        the 4th of march 2019 can be:
        04 03 2019
        4.3.2019 or 4.3.19
    </string>
    <string name="hint3EPA">On some devices the number pad has letters on each key.
    </string>
    <string name="hint1MPA">When hiding codes in the phone book people often name the contact in accordance with the company or site that it is used for</string>
    <string name="hint2MPA">When hiding codes as a contact the name will sometimes be the code in a word form however the contact can be left empty</string>
    <string name="tfamitigations">These tokens should be completely randomised and should not follow any distinguishable pattern. The use of a time-based randomisation methods or algorithms to calculate the next code makes it easy to predict what the next code will be, using the current time. Instead, a randomisation function should be used to create a unique token not based on any pattern or other value as to avoid repetition or the chances of this token falling into the wrong hands and being used by an attacker to access a user\'s account.
    </string>
    <string name="pamitigations">Due to the fact that the authentication of pins and passwords can only be as strong as the user\'s pin or password this can be problematic if the user stores their pins in obvious places or use words/phrases that are easily identifyable to the user. This can be prevented by using pins that do not relate to the user in any way. Increasing pins also helps as there can be far more combinationsfor possible pins that an attacker will have to try.
    </string>
    <string name="paeinstructions">However safe a log-in system can be made, if a user does not hide their pins or creates their
        pins from easily identifiable information, the system can be easily bypassed.

        To gain the flag use the user\'s social media account to figure out their pin
    </string>
    <string name="paminstructions">Due to the number of passwords and pins people have to remember, ways of noting down pins are
        often done such as including a contact in their phone to remind them of their pin. Using the user phone book on this emulator search the contacts to find the hidden pin code</string>
    <string name="sqliEInfo">You have been provided the email whale@whalemail.sea, use this login to gain as much information as possible. This level shows how user data is stored insecurely and poorly verified. This field does not implement a lockout policy alongside allowing account enumeration. Account enumeration allows a hacker to identify active accounts by brute force, allowing active accounts to be easily identified. Show you understand how to enumerate accounts!</string>
    <string name="sqliEHintOne">You have been given the email whale@whalemail.sea, try entering this on the login
        screen
    </string>
    <string name="sqliEHintTwo">This page is vulnerable to account enumeration, remember that means you can show what
        emails exist and which do not!
    </string>
    <string name="sqliEHintThree">Enter fish@whalemail.sea, note what happens to your success message.</string>
    <string name="sqliMInfo">You are a hacker who has been sniffing your victim’s network, viewing the codes they have
        been using to log in to their account. You must find the pattern in these codes and use this to predict what the
        next code will be. Once you have found this next code, you can use it to log in. Your findings from sniffing the
        network can be found in Hint 1.
    </string>


</resources>
