<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WhaleTheDvaa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vulnerability_selection">Vulnerability Selection</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vuln_selection">Vulnability Selection</string>
    <string name="flag">Enter Flag</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tfa_killer">tfaKiller</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="viewSocial">Victim\'s Social account</string>
    <string name="AboutTheWhale">White Hat Application for Learning and Evaluation, or WHALE, is a tool to help you learn about how common Android app vulnerabilities can be exploited and mitigated. This app aims to help you understand how you can develop secure Android applications by avoiding common design flaws or protecting against common attacks, as well as improve your skills as a penetration tester conducting an evaluation of an app’s security.
    </string>
    <string name="flags">The progress page is where you can enter the flags you have found from the vulnerabilities. You can find this page through the main vulnerability selector, or the difficulty selector for each vulnerability. Press ‘Enter Flag’ to add the flag you have found. You can view your progress in the progress bars which display how many of the vulnerabilities you have completed overall, as well as broken down by difficulty level.
    </string>
    <string name="l33tSpeak">When you have successfully exploited a vulnerability, you will find a flag – a piece of text in leet speak, or “L33T SP34K”, such as 4PPL3S or B4N4N4S. Once you have this flag, enter it in the progress page to update your progress.
    </string>
    <string name="mitigation">On the difficulty selector page, you can view how your chosen vulnerability is caused and commonly mitigated. This explains which flaws allow an attacker to exploit the application, and how they can be fixed to prevent these kind of attacks.
    </string>
    <string name="vulnerabilties">When you select ‘Get Splashing’, you will be directed to the vulnerability selection page. Here you will see the range of common Android vulnerabilities WHALE offers for you to try and exploit, each with varying levels of difficulty – easy, medium, and ‘killer’.
    </string>
    <string name="hints">Each vulnerability comes with three hints that can be viewed by selecting the ‘Hints’ button in the top right. The three hints will progressively give away more clues as to how you can exploit the vulnerability and get the flag.
    </string>
    <string name="information">At the top right of each page is the information button whcih gives information about the vulnerability. This will give you your scenario as a hacker trying to exploit the app, including any of the details about your victim you may need, such as their email address. This will appear when you open the vulnerability, as well as any time you click this button.
    </string>
    <string name="progress">The progress page is where you can enter the flags you have found from the vulnerabilities. You can find this page through the main vulnerability selector, or the difficulty selector for each vulnerability. Press ‘Enter Flag’ to add the flag you have found. You can view your progress in the progress bars which display how many of the vulnerabilities you have completed overall, as well as broken down by difficulty level.
    </string>
    <string name="instructions">instructions
    </string>


</resources>
